Welcome back.
So in this section, we are going to actually implement our system service.
So in the previous tutorials, we created these files.
Okay.
So and in the first tutorial, we saw the steps.
So now we are going to implement.
Let's now get to Framework Base GA.
Java Android App.
Okay.
Framework Base Core.
Java Android app.
Okay, so we are all here.
Okay.
Let's move this along here and.
Yeah.
So basically we need to copy our ideal file.
Java and the other two java files over here.
So the manager files, basically.
So inpatient.
All the three files.
All we have.
Okay.
So that looks.
Okay, so our first step is done.
And in the next step to create the service class, which is under this part framework based services,
call Java, call Android server framework, base services core and also.
Okay, so we are already here.
So this is the part.
Let me copy this file, which is actually in the service file.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, so let's turn.
This part is done, and now we basically need to go ahead and register the service.
Okay.
So now I registered the service in Pretoria.
So in the system, service and industry don't cha wa.
I need to basically copy this thing.
So when we actually.
So this is under base score android app.
It should be something here.
So it's actually system service registry.
That's why we're here.
Okay, let me be still.
So I am doing is I am registering the service amid a context and or service and the under service class
and then a computer.
The context framework based core Java Android content, Android content and intake content is the context
and the context.
I will just add my service.
So let's scope it somewhere here.
Let's start here.
And also is so I'm just putting it under all the services of these different services available in areas.
So I'm just adding one more, which is actually Android service.
Okay.
So now I need to do one more thing.
So I just copy that.
And then also I need to create one static string, all of them.
Best.
Sure.
Him.
Okay.
So this is basically the name of the service.
So here you are, just naming it as Android.
Okay.
So you're going to see this actually want to see a semi start churning.
You're going to see that actually, I assure you that in the later section.
Now we have more info on these two files and the third one is actually coming under from would be services.
Framework base and services on the services.
Java comb, charming comb.
Okay, here you'll go.
This is fine.
Okay, so.
And here.
So here, I need to just.
Cupid.
Just copy.
Don't let him.
And so it's basically this is just the package and no class name.
So his name and then copy the code.
Under and stone bootstraps obviousness.
I can.
So we modified the three files.
So our needs for the System Series Registry, where we have used the register service to register our
service.
And then in the context we defined those constants where we declared our service name and all those
stuffs.
And finally we called or added the new service in the start bootstrap services function.
So now let's go ahead and build it.
Improved selections.
Okay, Launch and values is six.
16.
Okay.
So we have one failure.
So that is in Android.
So it's manageable.
I think there is some syntax error.
So that's in a framework base cause our.
Okay.
So on Carlebach it is amazing.
Sorry.
Okay.
Yeah.
Finally, the build is successfully completed.
Let's run the simulator now.
Okay.
So now let's check our blocks first.
So what I'm doing is I'm just pushing my logcat logs into logcat or text in my road folder.
Okay.
And let's check whether there is any ceiling failure.
So there is a failure for a ceiling X and this is ourselves actually, since we haven't defined any
ACL in its policies.
This one is going to obviously fail.
Okay.
So why do we need to do is actually we need to create one policy to allow this series to be launched.